{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190368092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190368092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190368098","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190368098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190368488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190368487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190376590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190376590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190378445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190378445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190378877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190378877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190379361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190379361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190380004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190380004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190384080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190384080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190385195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190385194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190386814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190386814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190387955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190387955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190391432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190391431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190391923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190391922"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190392108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190392108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190393146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190393145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190394968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190394968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190395064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190395064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190395933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190395932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190396358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190396358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190397196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190397195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190399637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190399637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190399790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190399790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190405518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190405518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 6d6fba31-c905-40ea-a1b6-51ddf2486e57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190427416","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190427416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hasira_hasira_hakika_hawana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190434056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190434056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hajui_hayo_hajui_hatua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190440681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190440681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hakuweza_hakujali_hakupata_hakuweza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190448180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190448179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hakuweza_hakujali_hakupata_hakuweza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190454855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190454854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hawakuweza_hayo_hawezi_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190461503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190461501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hamu_hamu_harufu_hakupata"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190468127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190468127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hawana_hapo_hawakujua"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190474747","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190474747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hawakuweza_hawakuweza_haraka_hakujua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190481335","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190481334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hamu_harufu_hamu_hana"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190487930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190487930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hata_haha_halikuwa_hata"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190494551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190494551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hawakuwa_hakujua_hawakuwa_hadithi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190507690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190507690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" eb9cf39e-d2e0-408b-81c1-ef96afba852b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hawakuwa_hakujua_hawakuwa_hadithi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190513862","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190513862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 3ea4d9eb-68be-4fc6-8cb3-114cb042119f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190532213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190532212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 3ea4d9eb-68be-4fc6-8cb3-114cb042119f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190535056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190535052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 3ea4d9eb-68be-4fc6-8cb3-114cb042119f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190535170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190535170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 3ea4d9eb-68be-4fc6-8cb3-114cb042119f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190549046","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190549046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_hana-wetu-boga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190557585","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190557585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_nini-hana-baba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190566177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190566177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hayo_papo-hayo-kazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hayo"," userResponse":" hayo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190574265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190574265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hadi_hadi-pana-wapi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hadi"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190583396","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190583396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hadi_mawe-tatu-hadi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hadi"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190591767","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190591767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hapa_hapa-lala-kipi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hapa"," userResponse":" hapa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190600360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190600360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_pole-haha-babu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190609201","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190609201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hadi_koko-hadi-pesa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hadi"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190617906","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190617906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_mume-haha-tuwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190626654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190626654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_yeye-haki-mara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haki"," userResponse":" haki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190632402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190632401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_yeye-haki-mara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190638723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190638723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_yeye-haki-mara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190648217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190648217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_133910"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_yeye-haki-mara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}